me checking in
bastion you would make the perfect
research assistant
mei i love reading your journal i'm so
jealous you get to go to all those
places
that's true i guess you don't get to
travel very much
i get cold just looking at you then you
should look somewhere else
you're just no good bully how can you
even look at yourself in the mirror
i beg your pardon i consider myself a
freedom fighter a
misunderstood one i hate bullies like
you
that's cold you
are terrible that's cold
hey mccree do you know what time it is
well i'd say it's about
now i see what you're doing there
dr ziegler i don't think you've aged a
day since i last saw you
and neither have you may
may you haven't aged a day what's your
secret
cryostasis but i'm not sure if i'd
recommend it
look at all the snow we should make snow
angels
why are you looking at me mei
dr zhao i'm interested in your
colleagues research
into the long-term effects of cryogenic
freezing oh
well yes i'm sure
maybe
arisa you are adorable i will
pass your feedback on to iffy i believe
that she will be pleased
the front lines are no place for a
scientist
i guess it's a good thing to have you to
watch my back
i was wondering if i could take a look
at your little robot
i suppose so just keep that hammer to
yourself
chaser you're so amazing you inspire me
mei you're the real hero
aren't you weren't wearing all that yes
but it's too late to change
i love your glasses so cute oh
um thanks i like yours too
we should compare notes sometime that
would be great
what's your opinion on the toblestein's
gravitational models
may is this where you were stationed
before
me oh it's nothing winston
may if you don't have anything else
going on
you should come celebrate the holidays
with tracer emily athena and me
i'd love to we could have hot pot
winston what are your plans for the
holidays
you should come to gibraltar with tracer
emily athena and me
zarya i don't understand how you can
fight in the code wearing so
little i'll tell you my secret if you
give me your coat
zarya how can you even pick up all that
weight
i lift as well as i lift because it
cannot be avoided
winston you're so awesome just like soon
no wisdom symbol geometry
cheers love maze here
one shot one kill
i still love you snowboard delivered
too easy
you can argue with me but you can't
argue with data
and the data says you're incredibly
annoying